{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","address":"18400 W Warren","zipcode":"48228","owner":"Warren Food Groups LLC","licenseNumber":"204143","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":null,"establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":null,"riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E61000004822B24A14CE54C088563749F92B4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44098","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","inspectionDate":"2018-11-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"112","pcount":"1","pfcount":"3","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"4","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44098","inspectionDate":"11/8/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make available at all times."},{"inspectionid":"44098","inspectionDate":"11/8/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"CUSTOMER ORDER AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"inspectionid":"44098","inspectionDate":"11/8/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"The Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use of hand sink for this use and use appropriate sink."},{"inspectionid":"44098","inspectionDate":"11/8/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"inspectionid":"44098","inspectionDate":"11/8/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"44098","inspectionDate":"11/8/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"inspectionid":"44098","inspectionDate":"11/8/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"}]},{"inspectionid":"42066","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","inspectionDate":"2018-04-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"112","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42066","inspectionDate":"4/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"4-901.11","violationDescription":"After cleaning and SANITIZING, EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS shall be air-dried or used after adequate draining.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Clean equipment and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored/stacked wet","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Completely air dry all items prior to storage/use."},{"inspectionid":"42066","inspectionDate":"4/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"inspectionid":"42066","inspectionDate":"4/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"The Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use of hand sink for this use and use appropriate sink."}]},{"inspectionid":"36556","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","inspectionDate":"2016-08-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Pre-opening","inspectorid":"112","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36556","inspectionDate":"8/18/2016","inspectionType":"Pre-opening","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36556","inspectionDate":"8/18/2016","inspectionType":"Pre-opening","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36556","inspectionDate":"8/18/2016","inspectionType":"Pre-opening","establishmentid":"5324","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5324"}}